in this tutorial I'll be demonstrating
在本教程中，我将演示
how you can create these six icon
如何创建这六个图标
designs using nothing but basic shapes
只使用基本形状的设计
in inkscape before we get started though
在我们开始之前，在Inkscape中
if you want to learn more about how
如果您想了解更多有关如何
inkscape Works be sure to check out my
Inkscape作品一定要查看我的
inkscape master class it's a collection
Inkscape大师类，它是一个集合
of over 80 videos where we go over all
在80多个视频中，我们浏览了
of the tools and features in inkscape
Inkscape中的工具和功能
and I explain what they are and
我解释了它们是什么，并
demonstrate how they work we even have a
演示它们是如何工作的，我们甚至有一个
private Community where you can ask
私人社区，您可以在那里提问
questions and get help from me anytime
任何时候都可以向我提问并寻求帮助
you
你
want so the first thing I'm going to
所以我要做的第一件事就是
demonstrate is how to draw a heart so
演示的是如何画出一颗心
let me grab the squares and rectangles
我来拿正方形和长方形
tool I'll click and drag on the canvas
工具我将在画布上单击并拖动
to draw a vertically elongated rectangle
绘制垂直拉长的矩形
and then I'll grab my selection tool and
然后我会拿起我的选择工具
I want to make sure I have this lock
我想确保我有这把锁
icon turned off up here in the toolbar
在工具栏中此处关闭的图标
and for the width I want the width to be
对于宽度，我希望宽度是
100 pixels and I want the height to be
100像素，我想要的高度是
pixels and then I'm going to zoom in on
像素，然后我要放大
this object I'm going to go back to my
我要把这件物品放回我的
rectangle tool and I'm going to grab
矩形工具和我要抓取
this circular knot right here and bring
这个圆形结就在这里，并带来
this all the way down so that we have
这一路往下走，所以我们有
rounded edges like that
像这样的圆边
then I'll grab my selection tool I'll
然后我会拿起我的选择工具我会
right click the object and go to
右键单击该对象并转到
duplicate I will rotate it
复制，我会旋转它
90° select both objects click on them to
90°选择这两个对象，单击它们以
get the rotation handles and then hold
拿起旋转手柄，然后按住
your control key and grab the rotation
按下Ctrl键并抓取旋转
handle in the corner here and rotate it
将手柄放在角落里，然后旋转它
around until it's upright like that
直到它像那样直立起来
where it sort of looks like an X and now
它看起来有点像X，而现在
you can go into your shape Builder tool
您可以进入Shape Builder工具
make sure you have the addition option
确保您有添加选项
enabled and click and drag to draw a
启用并单击并拖动以绘制
line going through the area of the
穿过这一区域的线路
shapes to draw a heart now you can go
形状画出一颗心，现在你可以走了
back to your selection tool and just
返回到您的选择工具，只需
like that you've drawn a
就这样，你画了一个
heart now let's go over how you can draw
现在让我们来看看你是怎么画的
this waving flag icon I'm going to grab
我要抓住这个挥舞着的旗帜图标
my rectangle tool I'll click and drag on
我的矩形工具，我将点击并拖动
the canvas to draw a
画布以绘制
rectangle and I want to make sure that I
矩形和我想要确保我
have the edges rounded as I did for the
把边角弄圆，就像我为
previous object that we
我们之前的对象
created and then I'm going to draw
然后我要画一幅
another rectangle right about here and
另一个长方形就在这里
bring it out about that far
把它带到那么远
and I want to get rid of the rounded
我想去掉圆形的
edges here so I'll come up here and
边缘在这里，所以我会到这里来
click on this button in the
在中单击此按钮
toolbar I'll grab my selection tool move
工具栏我要抓起我的选择工具移动
this over about here and use this
这个在这里，用这个
scaling handle right here to size the
就在此处缩放手柄，以调整
rectangle appropriately about where it
适当地用矩形表示其所在位置
needs to be relative to the pole I'll
需要相对于杆子，我会
place this right about here we want a
把这个放在这里，我们想要一个
little bit of space to be between the
有一点空间可以放在
pole and the
杆子和杆子
flag once that's done let's create an
标记完成后，让我们创建一个
object to place on top of the flag for
要放置在旗帜顶部的对象
my example here I just used a star so I
在我的例子中，我只用了一个星号，所以我
will use that for this demonstration as
将在此演示中使用它作为
well but you can use whatever you'd like
嗯，但是你可以用任何你想用的东西
I'm going to grab my stars and polygons
我要去拿我的星星和多边形
tool I'm going to choose the star option
工具，我要选择星型选项
I want five corners and I want the spoke
我要五个角的，还有轮辐的
ratio to be
比率为
0.375 and the rounded and randomized
0.375和四舍五入的随机数
both set to zero and then I can click
都设置为零，然后我可以点击
and drag on my canvas to draw a star
拖到我的画布上画一颗星星
I'll hold control and
我会控制局面，
shift and bring my cursor straight up
按住Shift键并将光标垂直向上移动
like
喜欢
that and then I'll grab my selection
然后我会拿到我的选择
tool I'll place this in the center of
我会把这个放在
the
这个
rectangle to scale it down I'm holding
长方形来缩小它，我拿着
control and shift and clicking and
按住Ctrl键、Shift键并单击
dragging the
拖拽着
handle and to place this in the center
把手放在中间
of the rectangle I'll hold shift and
对于矩形，我将按住Shift并
click on the rectangle so that I have
点击矩形，这样我就有了
both object selected and I will open up
选中的对象和我都将打开
my aligned distribute menu by going to
我的对齐分发菜单，请转到
object and selecting aligned
对象并选择对齐
distribute I want to make sure I have
分发我想要确保我有
last selected chosen from this dropdown
从此下拉菜单中选择的最后一个选项
and I will Center it vertically and
我会把它垂直居中
horizontally
水平地
and then I will go to path and select
然后我将转到路径并选择
difference and it's going to subtract
不同之处，它将减去
the star from the rectangle so that it
长方形中的星星，所以它
creates a negative space area within it
在其内部创建负空间区域
now let me just place this over here to
现在让我把这个放在这里
readjust it I want to make these two
重新调整一下，我想做这两个。
corners of the rectangle rounded so let
矩形的角是圆角的，所以
me come over here to my nodes tool I'll
我来到我的节点工具前，我将
click on this icon up here that says add
点击此处的图标，上面写着添加
Corners live path effect and I'll click
角落实景路径效果，我将点击
on this node to select it and then hold
在此节点上选择它，然后按住
shift and click on this node to select
按住Shift键并单击此节点以选择
it with those two nodes selected you can
选择这两个节点后，您可以
grab these white knots right here and
抓住这些白色结，就在这里
click and drag them to round the corners
单击并拖动它们以绕过拐角
of the selected nodes now I'm going to
在选定的节点中，我现在要
bring that down a little more so it's
再降低一点，这样它就是
not too
不是太多
rounded right about there looks good and
在那里四舍五入看起来很好
once you're done with that you can click
完成后，您可以单击
on this Square icon up here to convert
在这里的这个正方形图标上转换
them to a path and that finalizes the
将它们添加到一条路径，并最终确定
effect now I'm going to give the flag a
效果现在我要给旗子一个
waving effect so to do that let me grab
挥手效果这样做，让我抓住
my selection tool I'm going to open up
我的选择工具，我要打开
the path effects menu by going to path
PATH Effects菜单转到PATH
and selecting path effects and from this
并选择路径效果，并从中
drop down over here I'm looking for
到这里来，我正在找
envelope deformation I'm going to select
我要选择封套变形
that and I want to uncheck this box
我想取消选中此框
right here that says enable left and
就在这里，上面写着启用左侧和
right paths and I'm going to select top
正确的路径，我将选择顶部
Bend path right here and I'm going to
就在这里转弯，我要
grab this top Edge and click and drag it
抓住此顶部边缘并单击并拖动它
up like that and then I'll click on this
像这样向上，然后我会点击这个
note over here and I'll take this handle
纸条在这里，我要这个把手
and bring this down like that so we want
像这样把它拿下来，这样我们就能
a little bit of a contour going on the
有一点轮廓在上面
top edge of the flag don't worry about
不要担心旗帜的顶端
what's happening on the left and right
左翼和右翼正在发生什么？
and down here that's going to come
而在这里，那将会到来
together once we finish making all of
一旦我们完成了所有的制作
these adjustments so I'm just going to
这些调整，所以我只是要
adjust this
把这个调一下
accordingly and then I want to do the
因此，然后我想做的是
same thing with the bottom Edge so I'll
底边也是一样，所以我会
come over here and select bottom path
到这里来，然后选择底部路径
and I'll do the same thing I'll take
我也会做我会做的事
this line and I'll bring this one up and
这条线，我会把这条线拿上来
I'll bring this one down so that the
我会把这个拿下来，这样
Contours are consistent on the top and
顶部的轮廓是一致的
the
这个
bottom and that looks good right there
底部，那里看起来很好
and once you're finish you can finalize
一旦你完成了，你就可以完成了
this by going to path and selecting
这是通过转到路径并选择
object to path and just like that you've
对象到路径，就像这样，你已经
created a waving FL FL
创造了一个挥舞的FL FL
icon now we'll go over how to create
图标现在我们将介绍如何创建
this wi glass shape so I'm going to grab
这个wi玻璃形状，所以我要抓起
my circles and ellipses tool and I'll
我的圆圈和椭圆工具，我会
click and drag on the canvas to draw an
在画布上单击并拖动以绘制一个
elongated ellipse like that and I'll
像这样拉长的椭圆形，我就会
make this black and I'm going to open up
把这个弄黑，我就会打开
my fill-in stroke menu by double
我的双倍填写笔画菜单
clicking the color stripe down here next
单击下一步此处的色条
to the fill label and I'll bring the
到填充物标签上，我会把
opacity of this down roughly in
它的不透明度大致降到了
half now I want to make a duplicate copy
现在一半我想复印一份
of this so let me go to my selection
所以让我来选我选的
tool I'll right click this and go to
工具，我将右键单击此工具并转到
duplicate and I'll hold my shift key and
复制一份，我会按住Shift键
I'll grab this top Arrow up here and
我拿着这个顶尖的箭头在这里
click and drag to scale this in and as
单击并拖动以将其放大并作为
long as you're holding shift it'll scale
只要你按住Shift键，它就会变大
inward from the top and bottom like that
像这样自上而下向内
and we want to make this about that
我们想把这件事做成这件事
height right about
高度约右
there and now I'm going to right click
现在我要右击
this and go to duplicate I'll hold
把这个拿去复印我拿着
control and bring this all the way down
控制并把这一切都带下来
here and I'll make this a little smaller
这里，我会把它弄小一点
by holding control and taking this top
通过控制和拿着这件上衣
arrow and scaling that down a little
箭头并将其缩小一点
bit and then I'm going to convert this
然后我要把这个转换成
to a path by going to path and selecting
通过转到路径并选择
object to path I'll grab the nodes tool
对象到路径，我将抓取节点工具
and I'll take this node right here and
我要把这个节点放在这里
click on it to select it and then hold
单击以将其选中，然后按住
control and click and drag it up about
控件，然后单击并向上拖动它约
that far and the same thing with this
那么远，这也是一样的事情
node I'll select this Noe and I'll click
Node我将选择此Noe，然后单击
and drag this up just a tiny bit though
把这个稍微往上拉一点
not much maybe about that far and this
不是很多，也许是关于那么远和这个
is going to be the base of the wine
将成为这款酒的基础
glass so now I'm going to grab the
玻璃，所以现在我要拿起
rectangle tool and I'm going to click
矩形工具，然后我将单击
and drag to draw a rectangle going
并拖动以绘制一个矩形
between the two objects here to
在这里的两个物体之间
represent the stem of the wine glass and
代表酒杯的杯柄和
I will make these Corners sharp by
我会让这些角落变得锋利
clicking on this
点击此按钮
button and I'll scale this down a little
BUTTON和我会把这个缩小一点
bit I'm going to hold my shift key and
我要按住我的Shift键
use this handle right here to scale that
就在这里使用这个手柄来缩放
down and I want to make sure I have
我想要确保我有
everything here centered so let me zoom
这里的所有东西都居中，所以让我放大
out let me select everything let come
出来，让我来选择一切，让我来
over here to my align and distribute
到这里来我的对准和分配
menu and make sure I have everything
菜单，并确保我带齐了所有东西
centered on the vertical
垂直居中
axis and now I can come over here into
轴心，现在我可以来到这里
the shape Builder tool and I can draw a
Shape Builder工具和我可以绘制一个
line through these areas to draw the
穿过这些区域的线，以绘制
shape shape that I'm trying to create
我想要创造的形状
and if I go back to the selection tool
如果我回到选择工具
now all we have to do is round these
现在我们要做的就是绕过这些
Corners in here so let me grab the nodes
在这里的角落里，让我抓住节点
tool and click on the object I'm going
工具，然后单击我要使用的对象
to select these four nodes right
要正确选择这四个节点
here I'll click on this button up here
在这里，我将点击这里的这个按钮
to add
要添加
Corners let me select them
角落让我来选择
again and I'll take this handle and
再来一次，我会拿着这个把手
bring this in or this white this little
把这个拿进来，或者这个白色的
round white knot and bring that in a
绕着白色的结，把它放在一个
little bit just to give a little bit of
一点点，只是为了给一点
a rounded rounded transition between the
之间的四舍五入过渡
stem and the other parts of the glass
玻璃杆和玻璃的其他部分
and now we can go back to the select
现在我们可以回到精选
tool and zoom
工具和缩放
out and now we can go to our fill and
现在我们可以尽情发挥了
stroke menu bring the opacity back up to
笔划菜单将不透明度恢复到
100% and there is our wine
100%，这是我们的酒
glass next we'll go over how to create
接下来，我们将介绍如何创建
this shopping cart icon so I'll come
这个购物车图标，所以我会来的
back into inkscape I'm going to grab my
回到Inkscape，我要拿起我的
beier pen which is located over here in
位于这里的贝尔钢笔
the toolbar or you can access it by
工具栏，也可以通过以下方式访问它
pressing the letter B on your keyboard
按键盘上的字母B
and up here in the tool settings menu I
在此处的工具设置菜单中
want to choose this option right here
要在此处选择此选项
that says create a sequence of straight
这就是说，创造一个笔直的序列
line segments and I want to click once
线段和我想要单击一次
on the canvas to create a point and then
在画布上创建点然后
hold the control key and bring the line
按住Ctrl键并拉线
straight across about that far and then
一直穿过大约那么远的地方，然后
click again to create another point and
再次单击以创建另一个点，然后
then I'm going to bring the line down
然后我要把绳子拉下来
about this far but I'm going to hold the
已经走到这一步了，但我要拿着
control key so that it locks it onto a
Ctrl键，以便它将其锁定到
75 degree angle and if you look in the
75度角，如果你往里看
status bar at the bottom of the screen
屏幕底部的状态栏
it'll show you which angle you currently
它会显示你当前的角度
have the line going at so if I move it
把绳子放在那里，所以如果我移动它的话
around you can see this angle changes I
在你周围你可以看到这个角度的变化
want the angle to be 75 degrees so I'll
我希望角度是75度，所以我会
move it about that far
把它移到那么远的地方
and again while I'm holding control
再一次，当我控制着局面
click to add a point and then bring this
单击以添加一个点，然后将此
line straight across about that far like
直线横跨大约那么远，就像
that and then press the enter key to
然后按Enter键以
close the path now we'll come over here
现在关闭小路，我们到这里来
to the stroke style tab under the fill
添加到填充下的笔触样式选项卡
and stroke Tab and I want to hold up on
笔划Tab和我想坚持下去
this plus icon to make this stroke
此加号图标以进行此笔划
thicker or give it a heavier
更厚或给它一个更重的
weight and I want it to have rounded
重量，我希望它是圆形的
caps as well so I'll click on this
帽子也是，所以我会点击这个
rounded caps button and I want it to
圆帽纽扣，我想让它
have rounded Corners as well or rounded
也有圆角或圆角
joins so I'll select that option as well
连接，因此我也将选择该选项
and now I'm going to grabb the rectangle
现在我要抓起长方形
tool let me press the Escape key to
工具使我可以按Esc键来
deselect everything there and I'll click
取消选中此处的所有内容，我将单击
and drag to draw a rectangle going over
并拖动以绘制一个经过的矩形
the object like
对象类似于
this and I'll convert that to a path by
这个和那个将通过以下方式转换为路径
going to path and selecting object to
转到路径并将对象选择到
path and I'll grab the nodes tool and
PATH，我将获取节点工具并
I'll take this node and bring this down
我要取下这个节点，把它取下来
and over like that we want the top Edge
就像这样，我们想要最顶尖的
and the right Edge going straight like a
右边缘就像一个笔直的
90° angle and then down here this bottom
90度角，然后往下走到这个底部
Edge dips down
边缘向下倾斜
and you can resize this as needed so I'm
你可以根据需要调整大小，这样我就
going to resize this I'm going to scale
我要调整这个的大小，我要调整
this down to make sure to hold the
这个放下来，以确保握住
control key while you scale it down to
Ctrl键，同时将其缩小到
preserve the aspect
保留纵横比
ratio and I noticed that this part of
Ratio和我注意到这部分
the cart down here sticks out a little
下面的手推车有点突出
too far so I'll grab my nodes tool and
太远了，所以我拿起我的节点工具
I'll just bring that node in a little
我只需要把那个节点放进去一点
bit and I'll hold control while I'm
比特和我会控制当我是
doing that so it locks it onto the
这样它就会将其锁定在
horizontal
水平
axis now I'll select the basket of the
轴现在，我将选择
cart and I'm going to apply the corner
Cart和我要申请转角
is life path effect as
生命路径效应是不是
well select each of these nodes by
我们将按以下方式选择这些节点
clicking on both of them or holding
同时点击两个按钮或按住
shift and clicking on both of them and
按住Shift键并同时单击这两个键和
then grab the white knot and bring that
然后抓住白色的结，带上那个
in like that just to give them rounded
这样做只是为了给他们四舍五入
Corners like
像这样的角落
that now I'm going to add some Wheels to
现在我要添加一些轮子到
the cart so let me grab the circles and
手推车让我抓起圆圈
ellipses tool I'll click and drag I'll
椭圆工具，我将点击并拖动，我将
hold the control key and click and drag
按住Ctrl键并单击并拖动
to draw a perfectly round circle like
画一个完美的圆形，就像
that grab the selection tool place it
抓取选择工具将其放置
right under the cart duplicate it by
就在购物车下面复制它
right clicking it and going to duplicate
右键单击它，然后复制
and then hold your control key and click
然后按住Ctrl键并单击
and drag this straight across like that
像这样把这个直接拖过去
and now what I'll do is for one final
现在我要做的是最后一次
step I'll click on this part of the cart
步骤：我将点击购物车的这一部分
go back to the nodes tool add the corner
返回到结点工具添加拐角
live path effect and then click on this
Live Path Effect，然后点击此
node right here and just make this
节点就在这里，然后把这个
rounded using that
用那个四舍五入
knot there we go once you're finished
结好了，你一打完，我们就走
you can click the square icon to convert
您可以单击正方形图标进行转换
this to a path and then you're going to
这是一条小路，然后你要
want to convert the stroke to a path as
我想将笔划转换为路径，如下所示
well so we'll go to path and select
那么我们将转到Path并选择
stroke to
笔划至
path and we can select everything now
路径，我们现在可以选择所有内容
and go to path Union and now we have a
然后转到Path Union，现在我们有一个
shopping cart
购物车
icon now let's go over how to create
现在让我们来看看如何创建
this sword
这把剑
icon I'm going to grab the circles and
图标我要抓起圆圈
ellipses tool and I'll hold my control
省略号工具，我会按住我的控件
key and click and drag to draw a
按住键并单击并拖动以绘制
perfectly round circle I'll grab my
完美的圆圈，我会抓起我的
selection tool move it towards the
选择工具将其移动到
bottom of the page click off of the
单击页面底部的
graphic to deselect it and then I'll
图形以取消选择它，然后我将
grab my rectangle tool and I'll click
抓起我的矩形工具，我会点击
and drag a rectangle going through the
并拖动一个矩形穿过
circle about that
绕着那个转一圈
wide and then I want to grab my
然后我想抓起我的
selection tool select both of these go
选择工具选择这两个GO
to the aligned distribute menu and
添加到对齐的“分发”菜单并
Center them up vertically click off of
将它们垂直居中单击关闭
it to deselect everything and I want to
它可以取消选择所有内容，我想
select just the rectangle here and hold
仅选择此处的矩形并按住
my shift key and use this right arrow to
我的Shift键，并使用此向右箭头
scale this down or up a little bit
将其缩小或放大一点
depending on how big or small your
取决于您的
rectangle is uh the idea is we want I'm
长方形是，呃，想法是我们想要我
paying attention to down here where this
请注意下面这一点
circle meets I want some of the circles
圆圈相遇我想要一些圆圈
sticking out between that from that
从那个突出到那个
rectangle there if I make it too big
长方形的，如果我把它做得太大的话
it's not quite obvious that there's a
这并不是很明显，有一个
circle there but if I make it smaller it
圆圈在那里，但如果我把它变小
looks a little out of place or too big
看起来有点不对劲或太大了
so I want to find a happy medium which I
所以我想找一个快乐的中间人
think is right about
认为是正确的关于
there and then once that's done I will
一旦做完了，我就会
bring this up a little more and I'm
再提这件事，我就
going to convert this to a path by going
要将其转换为路径，方法是
to path and selecting object to path and
到路径并选择要路径的对象和
then I'll grab my nodes tool and I want
然后我会拿起节点工具，我想
to select these two nodes up top over
要自上而下地选择这两个节点
here and I want to enable this setting
在这里，我想启用此设置
up here in the tool settings menu that
在此处的工具设置菜单中
says show transformation hand so I'll
说展示变身之手，所以我会
click on that to enable it and then I
单击以启用它，然后我
want to hold control and shift and grab
想要保持控制，按住Shift，然后抓取
this Arrow right here and scale this out
这个箭头就在这里，向外扩展
like that so that we make this we make
就像这样，这样我们就可以做我们自己做的
the top of this wider than the
这个的顶部比
bottom now we can disable that setting
现在我们可以禁用该设置
with these two nodes still selected we
在这两个节点仍被选中的情况下，我们
can come up here and select this button
可以出现在这里并选择此按钮
that says insert new nodes into selected
这表示将新节点插入到选定项中
segments and then click on just that new
细分市场，然后只点击那个新的
node right there and then hold your
节点就在那里，然后按住您的
control key and click and drag it up
Ctrl键并单击并向上拖动
like that to create the point of the
就像这样，创造了
sword so I'll bring it up a about that
剑，所以我会把它提出来。
far and now we'll create the handle of
现在，我们将创建句柄
the sword so I'll go back to my
所以我会回到我的
rectangle tool I'll click and drag to
我将单击并拖动到的矩形工具
draw rectangle about that
在上面画个矩形
size let me grab my selection tool and
大小让我拿起我的选择工具
reposition
重新定位
this I want to make sure everything here
这个，我想确保这里的一切
is centered so I'll select everything
居中，所以我将选择所有内容
Center it up
居中对齐
vertically and select just this object
垂直并仅选择此对象
right here and I'm going to convert this
就在这里，我要把这个转换成
to a path I'll go to path object to path
到一条路径，我将转到路径对象到路径
I'll go to my nodes tool and select
我将转到我的节点工具并选择
these two nodes no I'm sorry I'll add
这两个节点，不，对不起，我要加上
the cornner live path effect first and
角点活动路径效果首先和
then I will select these two nodes and
然后我将选择这两个节点并
bring this hand bring these Handles in
把这只手拿进来，把这些把手拿进来
like this so that we have rounded
像这样，所以我们有四舍五入
edges then we can convert that to a path
边，然后我们可以将其转换为路径
by clicking the square
通过单击该正方形
icon and now I want to create a little
图标，现在我想创建一个
bit of separation between the handle and
手柄和手柄之间有一点分离
the sword or the blade of the sword kind
剑或剑的刀刃
of like how I did over here you can see
就像我在这里做的那样，你可以看到
that separation there so to do that
那里的分离才能做到这一点
let me just take this object right click
让我把这个物体拿起来，右击
it go to duplicate make it white and
它去复制，使它变白
bring this up like that just click and
像这样打开它，只需点击并
drag this handle up and then click this
向上拖动此手柄，然后单击此
button that says lower selection one
显示较低选择一的按钮
step to lower it beneath the black
一步一步把它放在黑色下面
object and you can just take this handle
对象，您可以只使用此句柄
and make this in as big or as small as
把这个做得大一点或小一点
you'd like it to be it may help to zoom
你希望它是这样的它可能有助于放大
out and see exactly how it looks in
出来看看它到底是什么样子的
comparison to the rest of the objects
与其他对象的比较
and once you're happy with the size just
一旦你对尺寸感到满意，就
hold shift and click on the blade and go
按住Shift键并单击刀片即可执行操作
to path difference
到路径差
then you could select everything and go
然后你可以选择所有的东西，然后走
to path
至路径
Union and now you have created a sword
联盟，现在你创造了一把剑
icon and for the final part of this
图标和本部分的最后一部分
tutorial I will demonstrate how to
教程，我将演示如何
create this book
创建这本书
icon so to do this I'm going to grab my
为了做到这一点，我要拿起我的
stars and polygons tool I want to come
星形和多边形工具我想来
up here to the toolbar and choose the
点击此处到工具栏，然后选择
polygon setting I want six corners and
多边形设置我想要六个角和
rounded and randomize both set to zero
四舍五入和随机化都设置为零
and then I'm going to hold control and
然后我会控制局面，
shift on my keyboard and click and drag
按住键盘上的Shift键并单击并拖动
up in an upward motion with my cursor so
用我的光标向上移动，所以
that I create a hexagon where the
我创造了一个六边形，在那里
corners are going up and down vertically
拐角垂直向上和向下
like that let me grab my selection tool
就像这样，让我拿起我的选择工具
and put this towards the center of the
把这个放到中心位置
page now I'm going to convert this to a
现在我要把它转换成一个
path by going to path and selecting
路径：转到路径并选择
object to path and I'll go to my nodes
对象到路径，我将转到我的节点
tool and I want to select these nodes
工具和我想要选择这些节点
down here these three nodes down here in
下面这三个节点在这里
the bottom hold your control key and
底部按住Ctrl键，然后
click and drag them up about that
点击并将它们拖到上面
far now I'm going to grab my selection
现在我要去拿我的选择
tool click on the object to get the
工具单击该对象以获取
rotation handles and hold your control
旋转手柄并按住您的控制
key and grab this corner handle and
键，抓住这个角把手，然后
rotate it left four steps so one 2 3
将它向左旋转四步，这样就是一二三
four and when you do that you should see
四个，当你这样做时，你应该看到
these left edges are flat against the
这些左边缘与
bounding box of the object
对象的边界框
selection now I'll grab my nodes tool
选择现在，我将抓起我的节点工具
select these three nodes up here hold my
在这里选择这三个节点，拿住我的
control key and click and drag these up
Ctrl键并单击并向上拖动
like
喜欢
that go back to my selection tool click
返回到我选择工具点击
on the object again to get the rotation
再次放置在对象上以获得旋转
handles and and now I'm going to hold
把手，现在我要拿着
control and rotate it four steps
控制并旋转它四个步骤
clockwise so in the other direction now
顺时针方向，所以现在是另一个方向
so this time I will go to the right 1 2
所以这次我要去右边的12号
3 four and again we're holding control
三、四、再一次，我们掌握着控制权
the whole time we do this to lock it
我们一直这么做是为了锁住它
into 15 Dee increments like
到15dee的增量，如
that and once that's done let's
一旦做完了，让我们
rightclick the object and go to
右键单击该对象并转到
duplicate and I want to make this a
复制，我想让它成为一个
different color just so I can
不同的颜色，这样我就可以
differentiate it I'm going to make this
区分它，我要做这个
green and then I'll rightclick this and
绿色，然后我会用鼠标右键点击
duplicate it again and I'll make this
再复制一次，我就做这个
one a different color as well so I'll
一个也是不同的颜色，所以我会
make this one red and I will turn on
把这个设为红色，我就会打开
snapping by clicking this magnet icon up
通过单击此磁铁图标向上进行捕捉
here in the top right corner of the
在这里的右上角
screen and I want to take this object
屏幕和我想要拿着这个物体
and just snap the corners there right
在那里折断角落就行了
about there like that so that the bottom
大概就在那里，所以底部
area this green kind of looks like a
这片绿色的区域看起来像一个
green check mark and once that's done
绿色复选标记，一旦完成
hold your shift key and click on the
按住Shift键并单击
green object so that you have both of
绿色物体，这样你就可以同时拥有
these objects selected here and go to
在此处选择这些对象并转到
path and select
路径并选择
difference now I'm going to use the
不同之处现在我将使用
offset path effects so let me come over
抵消路径效果，让我过去吧
here to my path effects menu if you
如果你想进入我的路径效果菜单
don't have a path effects menu just go
没有路径效果菜单，只需转到
to path and select path
要创建路径并选择路径
effects and the path effect I'm looking
效果和我正在寻找的路径效果
for is offset so I'm going to use this
For是偏移量，所以我将使用这个
search box right here and type off and
在这里的搜索框中输入Off和
there it is right there
就在那里，就在那里
offset I'll grab my nodes tool and I
偏移量我会拿起我的结点工具
will make sure first of all make sure
将首先确保确保
you have these options enabled down here
您已在此处启用了这些选项
we want the the join set to miter units
我们希望将连接集设置为斜接单位
this is not really important so you can
这并不重要，所以你可以
ignore that offset zero and miter limit
忽略偏移零和斜接限制
4 and then use these settings as well
4，然后也使用这些设置
and once that's set set I will grab this
一旦设置好，我就会拿到这个
red circle and click and drag this down
红色圆圈，然后单击并向下拖动
like
喜欢
that about that
关于那件事
far and once that's done you can go to
很远，一旦完成，你可以去
path object to path to finalize that and
将Path对象设置为路径，以完成该AND
now we can grab our selection tool
现在我们可以拿起我们的选择工具了
select both of these objects click on it
选择这两个对象，然后单击它
to get the rotation handle and hold your
要获得旋转手柄并按住您的
control key and rotate it to the right
Ctrl键并向右旋转
one two two steps like that now you can
一步、两步、两步，现在你可以
click off of it to deselect everything
单击该选项可取消选择所有内容
take just this green object grab your
拿着这个绿色的物体，抓起你的
nodes to tool and take these two nodes
要工具和获取这两个节点的节点
right here and hold your control key and
就在这里，按住你的控制键
click and drag them out like that we
点击并将它们拖出，就像我们
want this to to extend beyond that black
我想把这件事延伸到黑色之外
shape and now we can go back to our
现在我们可以回到我们的
selection tool select everything let me
选择工具选择一切让我
turn off the snapping Now by clicking
立即通过单击关闭捕捉
this magnet icon again and now I can
这个磁铁图标再一次，现在我可以
click on the object to get the rotation
单击对象以获得旋转
handles and now I'm going to hold
把手，现在我要拿着
control and rotate it to the left two
控件并将其向左旋转到两个
steps so one two and now I will go to
所以一二步，现在我要去
path difference and that right there is
路径差异，就在那里
the effect we're looking for so now I
我们正在寻找的效果，所以现在我
have to make the corners of these a
必须把这些角落变成一个
little rounded because as of right now
略显圆润，因为从现在开始
they're a little too Square so to do
它们有点太方了，所以不能这样做
that I'm going to grab my nodes tool
我要拿起我的节点工具
click on the book to select it add the
单击图书以将其选中，添加
corners live path effect and I'm going
角落生活的路径效应，我要去
to select these four nodes over here on
要在此处选择这四个节点
the left and I will grab one of these
我和左边的人去拿一个这个
handles one of these white knots and
处理这些白色结中的一个
scale that in like that just to make
像这样把它放大，就是为了
these Corners
这些角落
rounded and then I'll come over here and
四舍五入，然后我会走到这里
do the same thing I want to select these
做与我想要选择的相同的事情
three notes
三个音符
and give them a little bit of a rounded
给他们一点圆润的
Edge as
边为
well and then I'll come over here and do
好的，然后我会来这里做
the same thing select these nodes on the
同样的事情，选择在
right hand side and scale them down it's
在右手边，然后按比例缩小
good to scale each of these segments
扩展这些细分市场中的每一个都很好
individually because the amount that you
个别是因为你的金额
want around them is going to be
他们身边的渴望将会是
different for each side so it's you get
每一方都不同，所以你会得到
a better result doing it this way and
这样做会有更好的结果
I'll come up here and use this one as
我会到这里来，把这个当做
well so I'll click on that one and this
好的，我会点击那个，然后这个
should be the last one right here I'll
应该是这里的最后一个了，我会
I'll r that off a little
我会把这一点讲得更快一些
bit and there we go I'm going to click
然后我们开始了我要点击
on the square button up here to convert
在上面的方形按钮上进行转换
to a
到一个
path okay so there we go there's the
路径好的，所以我们去那里，那里是
book icon now one final part of the book
图书图标现在是这本书的最后一部分
icon if you notice here I put a little
图标如果你注意到我在这里放了一点
bit of a bookmark down there just to
下面有个书签，只是为了
emphasize that it's a book it makes it
强调这是一本书，它创造了它
look more like a book when you do that
当你这样做的时候，看起来更像是一本书
so to create that bookmark I'm just
所以为了创建书签，我只是
going to grab my rectangle tool and I'll
拿起我的矩形工具，我会
click and drag to draw a rectangle over
单击并拖动以在其上绘制一个矩形
this portion of the object I'm going to
物体的这一部分，我要
grab my selection tool click on it again
抓起我的选择工具再次点击它
to get the rotation handles but instead
来获取旋转手柄，但实际上
of rotating we're going to Shear we're
旋转，我们要切变，我们要
going to use the icon over here on the
我要使用这里的图标
right hand side and hold the option key
在右侧并按住OPTION键
or the ALT key if you're on Windows and
或者Alt键，如果您使用的是Windows并且
just bring this down two
只要把这个降下来两个
steps so that the edges match in
步长，以使边匹配
Direction like that and we can bring
像这样的方向，我们可以带来
this right about
这就是关于
there and I'm going to scale that down a
在这里，我将把它缩小到
little bit let me try that
让我试一试。
again and if you need to make the this
再说一次，如果你需要把这个
bottom longer or shorter I'm placing it
底部更长或更短我要把它放在
so that the top Edge goes halfway
这样顶端边缘就走到了一半
through the books pages here and I want
翻阅这里的书页，我想
this to be a little outside of the
这有点出格了
bottom so let me grab the nodes tool and
底部，让我抓起节点工具和
let me convert this to a path I'll go to
让我将其转换为一条我要转到的路径
path object to path and now I can take
路径对象到路径，现在我可以
those nodes and hold control and move
并按住控制并移动这些节点
them up like that and I can add new
就像这样，我可以添加新的
nodes in there as well with those two
这两个节点也在那里
nodes selected I can click on this
选定的节点我可以单击此选项
button over here that says add new
这里的按钮，上面写着添加新的
nodes and just select this node right
节点，只需选择此节点即可
here and move that up
给你，把那个往上移
and now I want to create a little bit of
现在我想要创造一点
an offset between the book and the
书本和
bookmark so let me make this black and
书签，让我把它变成黑色和
let me right click this and go to
让我右键单击它，然后转到
duplicate I'll make the duplicate copy
我会复印一份副本
white and I'll hold control and shift
怀特和我会保持控制和换挡
and scale it up and I want to lower it
把它放大，然后我想把它降低
beneath the black object so I'll click
在黑色物体下面，所以我会点击
on the lower selection one step and then
在下面的选择上一步，然后
I can just scale this up or down
我可以将其放大或缩小
depending on how much I want the offset
取决于我想要多大的偏移量
to be and again I'm holding control and
一次又一次，我掌控着一切
shift while I do this to scale it from
在我执行此操作时按Shift键以从
the center
中心
and then once you're happy with how it
一旦你对它的表现感到满意
looks hold shift and click on the book
查看按住Shift键并单击书本
and go to path
并转到路径
difference and now we can select both
不同，现在我们可以选择两者
objects and go to path Union and we have
对象，然后转到Path Union，我们有
created our book
创造了我们的书
icon so that should do it for today's
图标，所以这应该会在今天的
tutorial we have created all six of
我们已经创建了全部六个教程
these icons using nothing but simple
这些图标使用的只是简单
shapes in inkscape if you have any
Inkscape中的形状(如果您有
questions let me know and as always
问题让我知道，而且一如既往
thanks for watching join the logos by
感谢收看《加入标志》节目
Nick mailing list and get over 200 free
尼克邮寄名单和获得超过200免费
design templates including logos avatars
包括徽标化身的设计模板
textures infographics and more as a
纹理、信息图表等
member you'll receive news updates and
会员您将收到最新的新闻和
tips about your favorite design apps
关于你最喜欢的设计应用的小贴士
just use the link below to subscribe for
只需使用以下链接即可订阅
free and download your templates as
免费下载您的模板
always thanks for watching
永远感谢您的收看